healthinsiders.com 2011-09-02

# Privacy Policy

HealthInsiders.com (“The Site”) has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. This Web site provides health information and resources. We understand that health is a personal and private matter, and we do not want you to have to be concerned about the security or use of any information you provide to us. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for the Web site, HealthInsiders.com.

HealthInsiders.com does not sell, trade, or rent the personal identifying information of its users to third parties. HealthInsiders.com collects no personal identifying information about its users except when specifically and knowingly provided by such users. Many of the services on our site are offered without our collecting any personally identifiable information from you. You can visit HealthInsiders.com and view most of our sites content and sections while remaining anonymous. A user’s personal identifying information may be used by HealthInsiders.com to improve its services to its users. Users who have requested updates may receive information from HealthInsiders.com on new health therapies, products and services that may help them better manage their care. Any information received is not an endorsement or opinion of HealthInsiders.com regarding any treatment option, product or service. Users who receive a requested update, will always have the ability at any time to opt out of receiving any future information. HealthInsiders.com may offer its users online surveys and questionnaires that ask users for opinions and/or other information. Such surveys are completely voluntary. Any information submitted may be shared with other companies on an aggregate basis, but HealthInsiders.com will not provide such companies with any information regarding the identity of any individual user.

#### Passive Information Collection Practices

**Aggregate information:** Users should know that HealthInsiders.com may place a “cookie” in the browser files of the user’s computer. The cookie does not contain any personal identifying information. The information tracked provides information such as your browser type, the type of operating systems you use, the domain of your Internet service provider, and pages visited on the site. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but a user can usually modify their browser to prevent cookies from being accepted.

**IP Addresses:** An IP address is a number automatically assigned to your computer whenever you access the Internet. All computer identification on the Internet is conducted with IP addresses, which allow computers and servers to recognize and communicate with each other. The Company collects IP addresses in order to conduct system administration, report aggregate information to partners, sponsors and advertisers, and to conduct site analysis. To maintain visitor anonymity, the Company does not associate IP addresses with records containing personal information. However, the Company will use IP addresses to identify any visitors who refuse to comply with HealthInsiders.com ‘s rules or Terms and Conditions.

#### Active Information Collection

**About Children:** This site is not intended for children under the age of 13. We will not knowingly collect information from site visitors in this age group. We encourage parents to talk to their children about their use of the Internet and the information they disclose to Websites.

**Public Forums:** This site may make forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to Members. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and Members should exercise caution when deciding to disclose any personal information. We cannot control the actions of others and inappropriate and/or offensive information may be posted. We have scheduled monitoring of the message boards and when we come across inappropriate and/or offensive information we remove it.

**Passwords and Account Information:** You are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and/or account information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you are online.

**Email Opt-Out:** Our site provides users with the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners or sponsors at the point where we request information about the visitor. This site also gives users the following options for removing their name from our communications list so as to not receive future communications or to discontinue service:

You can click “Unsubscribe” at the bottom of all emails communications from Company.

#### Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Certain areas of the site are secured with encryption technology. Any employee or contractor requiring access to technology relating to Member information must be given password access by the Company management. This access is reviewed on a regular basis, and parties granted such access are instructed on the Company privacy and security policies. In order to prevent loss of information, all data is backed up on a real-time basis.

#### Contact Information

Site visitors who have questions about this privacy statement, the privacy practices of this site, or their dealings with this Web site insofar as their privacy and confidentiality are concerned, should contact [admin@healthinsiders.com](mailto:admin@healthinsiders.com)This email address is being protected from spam bots, you need Javascript enabled to view it . This email address is being protected from spam bots, you need Javascript enabled to view it.

#### Changes to This Privacy Policy

If this Privacy Policy changes, the revised policy will be posted on this site. Please check back periodically, and especially before you provide any personally identifiable information.

#### Google Adsense and Third Party Advertising

We use [Google AdSense](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/AdSense "Google AdSense") and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used, please click here: <http://www.google.com/privacy.html>

#### DoubleClick Dart Cookies

Google AdSense uses the DoubleClick DART cookie to gather the information specified above. In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize cookies on your browser. You may decline to provide personal information to them and/or refuse cookies in your browser, although some of features may not function properly as a result. For more information on the DoubleClick DART cookie and privacy: <http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx>
